search4clicks.com 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy | PlattFormPartners.com

This is the web site of PlattFormPartners.com, a division of PlattForm Advertising, Inc. For each visitor to our web site, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and not the e-mail address (unless you explicitly and voluntarily submit it to us). The e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, are only used for internal uses and then are discarded. This information is used in the following ways:

  * To improve the content of our web site.
  * To notify consumers about updates to our web site.

We collect no information from individuals below the age of 13. Information you share on our web site will not be shared with outside parties unless you provide us with approval to do so. Please read the terms of contests and other offers as the consent may be part of the entry into a contest. We do not sell information to others, but may share some information with our partners, when we have your consent. If you do not wish for us to share information with our partners, please send an e-mail to [partners@plattformad.com](mailto:partners@plattformad.com) to unsubscribe.

### Cookies

We use cookies solely for the purpose of storing visitors' preferences. We keep the size of the cookies as small as possible, and set the cookies only when it is absolutely necessary for our software to perform tasks.

  * If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail message to us at [partners@plattformad.com](mailto:partners@plattformad.com).
  * If you share your mailing address with us online, the mailing address will only be used in the manner you specified when you provided that information.
  * If you share your telephone number with us online, you will only receive telephone calls from us with information regarding any orders you have placed with us.
  * Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page. We encourage you to check our privacy policy occasionally so you will be aware of our practices and policies.

### Change to Terms

We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

### Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer-sensitive data. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personally-identifiable information that we have collected at our site.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, we encourage you to contact us.

### Contact Information:

PlattForm Advertising

15500 W. 113th St.Suite 200

Lenexa, KS 66219

Phone: (913) 254-6000

E-mail: [partners@plattformad.com](mailto:partners@plattformad.com)
